Krishnareddy Yojana

• 9-6-42, Police Line, Sullurupeta., 524121 Nellore, India

Krishnareddyyojana4a2@gmail.com

\+919100190800

Skills

JAVA
Angular
HTML
CSS
C Language
Server Management
Admin Skills
LIMS and ERDS

Languages

- Telugu
- . English
- ▲ Hindi

Strength

- Logical Thinking
- · Problem Solving
- * Patience
- Perseverance
- Communication

(4) Interests

- Learning new Languages
- Sketching
- Traveling

Profile

A Technical professional with an overall experience of 2.6 years targeting to work as a professional with a growing organization for a challenging and responsible position that utilizes and nurtures my technical, managerial, and analytical skills, providing sample opportunity for personal growth.

Education

B.Tech, Ramireddy Subbarami Reddy Engineering College 2015 - 2019 | Nellore, AP

Board of Intermediate Education, *NARAYANAJr. COLLEGE* 2013 - 2015 | Nellore, Ap

Board of secondary Education, *HOLYCROSS HIGHSCHOOL* 2013

Professional Experience

Current work experience:

Analyst, HCL Technologies LTD

01/2021 - present | Chennai, India

Active Directory - Create, Delete and manage a user (Starter/Leaver Requests), Admin, Service, Shared folder Access, OU movement.

Intel - Troubleshoot the Resource (Memory, CPU, Drive) alerts and extension of resources in VC and Server.

- Validation of servers and application after Patching activity.
- Perform the initial troubleshooting for Printer related issues and coordinating with Vendors.
- Folder Access Management (Creation, Modification, Deletion) and Restoration of files/folders.
- Permission Management of File shares in Varonis tool.

Citrix - Troubleshooting Login Gateway (MFA), Excel, Teams, VHD, Keyboard, Browser related issues.

• Home drive management - Creation, Modification, Deletion.

Exchange - Create/Delete/Modify (User mailbox, contacts, Distribution list, Security Groups, Shared mailbox, POP3, Rooms)

- License management in Microsoft 365 Admin center and Azure Active Directory.
- Enabling of Mail forwarding to external and internal users.
- Troubleshooting Outlook application, mailbox related issues.
- Blacklist/Whitelist of Domains and mail address.
- Adding, Removing Mailbox and Calendar delegation.
- Enabling Out of Office message to internal and external users.
- Lotus Notes Create, Delete and manage person Document.

Telephony (AVAYA) - Creation/Deletion/Managing of Station ID, Agent Login ID.

- Creation/Deletion/Managing of Right FAX account.
- Performing Health checks of various technologies–Intel, Citrix, Exchange, IEM.

Previous work experience:

CANDOR SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS:

Designation: Associate Software Engineer Duration: 2-01-2020 to 15-01-2021.

WORKINGDETAILS: LIMS and ERDS. LIMS (Laboratory information Management System) with this software we can automate workflows, integrate instruments, and manage samples and associated information in pharmacy labs. This role is a key role in my life in which we need to be more concentrated because it costs others life.

Name of the project: worked on LIMS and ERDS it is a pharmacy software worked nearly 30 codes in KRSG site, 10 codes in SEML, 2 codes in pandy, 10 in ALATHUR

Projects in College

- Presented a paper on "VIRTUALREALITY
- Presented a paper on "VOICEMARPHING
- Attended for a workshop on" INTERNET OF THINGS"

INTERNSHIP

- Carried INTERNSHIP on "RADAR" at RANGEOPERATIONS(RO) in Satish Dhawan Space Center SHAR.
- Done reach on the VLSI project "ANEFFICIENT VLSI ARCHITECTURE FOR CONVOLUTION BASED DWT USING MAC